[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What is 5 + 3?",
        "answers": [
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9
        ],
        "correct_answer": 8
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What is 10 + 7?",
        "answers": [
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18
        ],
        "correct_answer": 17
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What is 12 + 4?",
        "answers": [
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17
        ],
        "correct_answer": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What is 20 + 5?",
        "answers": [
            23,
            24,
            25,
            26
        ],
        "correct_answer": 25
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What is 7 + 8?",
        "answers": [
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17
        ],
        "correct_answer": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "What is 3 + 9?",
        "answers": [
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14
        ],
        "correct_answer": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What is 15 + 6?",
        "answers": [
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23
        ],
        "correct_answer": 21
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "What is 18 + 7?",
        "answers": [
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27
        ],
        "correct_answer": 25
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "What is 9 + 8?",
        "answers": [
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19
        ],
        "correct_answer": 17
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "What is 11 + 13?",
        "answers": [
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25
        ],
        "correct_answer": 24
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "What is 5 + 10?",
        "answers": [
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17
        ],
        "correct_answer": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "What is 4 + 16?",
        "answers": [
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21
        ],
        "correct_answer": 20
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "What is 8 + 11?",
        "answers": [
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21
        ],
        "correct_answer": 19
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "What is 13 + 12?",
        "answers": [
            24,
            25,
            26,
            27
        ],
        "correct_answer": 25
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "What is 2 + 9?",
        "answers": [
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13
        ],
        "correct_answer": 11
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "What is 14 + 5?",
        "answers": [
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21
        ],
        "correct_answer": 19
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "What is 6 + 8?",
        "answers": [
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16
        ],
        "correct_answer": 14
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "What is 17 + 4?",
        "answers": [
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22
        ],
        "correct_answer": 21
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "What is 7 + 14?",
        "answers": [
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23
        ],
        "correct_answer": 21
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "What is 12 + 9?",
        "answers": [
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23
        ],
        "correct_answer": 21
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "What is 5 + 18?",
        "answers": [
            21,
            22,
            23,
            24
        ],
        "correct_answer": 23
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "What is 3 + 15?",
        "answers": [
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19
        ],
        "correct_answer": 18
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "What is 11 + 5?",
        "answers": [
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17
        ],
        "correct_answer": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "What is 10 + 6?",
        "answers": [
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18
        ],
        "correct_answer": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "What is 9 + 12?",
        "answers": [
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22
        ],
        "correct_answer": 21
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "What is 7 + 13?",
        "answers": [
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22
        ],
        "correct_answer": 20
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "What is 14 + 8?",
        "answers": [
            20,
            21,
            22,
            23
        ],
        "correct_answer": 22
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "What is 3 + 11?",
        "answers": [
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16
        ],
        "correct_answer": 14
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "What is 2 + 7?",
        "answers": [
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11
        ],
        "correct_answer": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "What is 6 + 13?",
        "answers": [
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21
        ],
        "correct_answer": 19
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "What is 5 + 14?",
        "answers": [
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21
        ],
        "correct_answer": 19
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "What is 4 + 7?",
        "answers": [
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13
        ],
        "correct_answer": 11
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "What is 12 + 6?",
        "answers": [
            17,
            18,
            19,
            20
        ],
        "correct_answer": 18
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "What is 9 + 10?",
        "answers": [
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21
        ],
        "correct_answer": 19
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "What is 8 + 5?",
        "answers": [
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15
        ],
        "correct_answer": 13
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "What is 7 + 6?",
        "answers": [
            11,
            12,
            13,
            14
        ],
        "correct_answer": 13
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "What is 4 + 13?",
        "answers": [
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18
        ],
        "correct_answer": 17
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "What is 3 + 14?",
        "answers": [
            16,
            17,
            18,
            19
        ],
        "correct_answer": 17
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "What is 11 + 8?",
        "answers": [
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21
        ],
        "correct_answer": 19
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "What is 10 + 4?",
        "answers": [
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16
        ],
        "correct_answer": 14
    }
]
